export const flexboxData = {
  set4: {
    title: `Flexbox`,
    flashcards: {
      "4_1": {
        question: `**Question:** How many dimensions is the flexbox layout?`,
        answer: `**Answer:** 1-dimensional\n
    \nFlexbox deals with layout in one dimension at a time -- either as a row or a column.`,
      },
      "4_2": {
        question: `**Question:** What are the 2 axes of flexbox?`,
        answer: `**Answer:** The **main** axis and the **cross** axis.`,
      },
      "4_3": {
        question: `**Question:** Which axis defines \`flex-direction\`?`,
        answer: `**Answer**: The **main** axis defines \`flex-direction\``,
      },
      "4_4": {
        question: `**Question:** What are the values available for \`flex-direction\`?`,
        answer:
          `**Answer:** The values available for \`flex-direction\` are\n` +
          `- \`row\`\n- \`row-reverse\`\n- \`column\`\n- \`column-reverse\``,
      },
      "4_5": {
        question: `**Question:** Which direction does \`flex-direction: row || row-reverse\` run?`,
        answer: `**Answer:** \`row\` || \`row-reverse\` will run along the row in the **inline** direction`,
      },
      "4_6": {
        question: `**Question:** Which direction does \`flex-direction: column || column-reverse\` run?`,
        answer: `**Answer:** \`column\` || \`column-reverse\` will run along the column in the **block** direction`,
      },
      "4_7": {
        question: `**Question:** What is an area of a document laid out using flexbox called?`,
        answer: `**Answer:** A **flex container**`,
      },
      "4_8": {
        question: `**Question:** How do you create a flex container?`,
        answer: `**Answer:** Set the value of the area's container to \`display: flex || inline-flex\``,
      },
      "4_9": {
        question: `**Question:** What are the direct children of a flex container called?`,
        answer: `**Answer:** **flex items**`,
      },
      "4_10": {
        question: `**Question:** What are the default values of a flex container?`,
        answer:
          `**Answer:** The default values of a flex container are\n` +
          `- Items display in a row (\`flex-direction: row\`)\n` +
          `- Items start from the start edge of the main axis\n` +
          `- Items do not stretch on the main dimension but can shrink\n` +
          `- Items will stretch to fit the main axis\n` +
          `- The \`flex-basis\` property is set to \`auto\`\n` +
          `- The \`flex-wrap\` property is set to \`nowrap\`\n`,
      },
    },
  },
};
